{
    "easy": [
        {
            "question": "Which British driver has the most Formula 1 World Championships to his name?",
            "options": ["Lewis Hamilton", "Jenson Button", "Nigel Mansell", "Damon Hill"],
            "correctOption": "Lewis Hamilton"
        },
        {
            "question": "In which European city were the 2012 Summer Olympics held?",
            "options": ["Paris, France", "Madrid, Spain", "Athens, Greece", "London, United Kingdom"],
            "correctOption": "London, United Kingdom"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is the most successful male tennis player in Wimbledon history?",
            "options": ["Roger Federer", "Rafael Nadal", "Novak Djokovic", "Andy Murray"],
            "correctOption": "Roger Federer"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which European golfer is known as the 'Spanish Armada' and has won numerous majors, including The Masters and The Open Championship?",
            "options": ["Sergio Garcia", "Miguel Ángel Jiménez", "José María Olazábal", "Seve Ballesteros"],
            "correctOption": "Seve Ballesteros"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which Six Nations team represents Wales in international rugby?",
            "options": ["The Red Roses", "The Shamrocks", "The Dragons", "The Pumas"],
            "correctOption": "The Dragons"
        },  
        {
            "question": "In cricket, which European country competes as a Full Member of the International Cricket Council (ICC)?",
            "options": ["England", "Ireland", "Scotland", "Netherlands"],
            "correctOption": "England"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which European country is famous for hosting the annual Four Hills Tournament in ski jumping?",
            "options": ["Norway", "Switzerland", "Germany", "Austria"],
            "correctOption": "Austria"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which country has won the most FIFA World Cup titles in Europe?",
            "options": ["Germany", "Italy", "France", "England"],
            "correctOption": "Italy"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which NBA team is known for its iconic green and white uniforms and is based in Boston?",
            "options": ["Los Angeles Lakers", "Miami Heat", "Boston Celtics", "Chicago Bulls"],
            "correctOption": "Boston Celtics"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which country is known as the 'Seleção' and has won the FIFA World Cup a record five times?",
            "options": ["Brazil", "Germany", "Argentina", "Italy"],
            "correctOption": "Brazil"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is the world-record holder in the men's 100-meter sprint, often regarded as the fastest man in the world?",
            "options": ["Carl Lewis", "Jesse Owens", "Ben Johnson", "Usain Bolt"],
            "correctOption": "Usain Bolt"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which driver, known as 'The Iceman,' hails from Finland and won the Formula 1 World Championship in 2007?",
            "options": ["Michael Schumacher", " Lewis Hamilton", "Kimi Räikkönen", "Sebastian Vettel"],
            "correctOption": "Kimi Räikkönen"
        }                   
    ],

    "medium": [
        {
            "question": "Who is the all-time leading scorer in NBA history?",
            "options": ["LeBron James", "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar", "Michael Jordan", "Kobe Bryant"],
            "correctOption": "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who holds the record for the most runs scored in a single Test cricket inning, with 400 not out?",
            "options": ["Sachin Tendulkar", "Brian Lara", "Ricky Ponting", "Don Bradman"],
            "correctOption": "Brian Lara"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which country won the UEFA European Championship in 2016?",
            "options": ["France", "Portugal", "Germany", "Spain"],
            "correctOption": "Portugal"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the youngest Formula 1 World Champion when he won the title in 2005?",
            "options": ["Sebastian Vettel", "Lewis Hamilton", "Fernando Alonso", "Michael Schumacher"],
            "correctOption": "Fernando Alonso"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is the NBA's all-time assists leader?",
            "options": ["Magic Johnson", "Steve Nash", "John Stockton", "Chris Paul"],
            "correctOption": "John Stockton"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which male tennis player has won the most Australian Open titles?",
            "options": ["Novak Djokovic", "Roger Federer", "Rafael Nadal", "Andre Agassi"],
            "correctOption": "Novak Djokovic"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who set the world record for the men's marathon with a time of 2:01:39 in 2018, a record that still stands as of 2023?",
            "options": ["Eliud Kipchoge", "Dennis Kipruto Kimetto", "Wilson Kipsang", "Haile Gebrselassie"],
            "correctOption": "Eliud Kipchoge"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which team has won the most Constructors' Championships in Formula 1 history?",
            "options": ["Ferrari", "Mercedes", "Red Bull Racing", "Williams"],
            "correctOption": "Mercedes"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which player is known as 'The Egyptian King' and plays for Liverpool FC?",
            "options": ["Mohamed Salah", "Sadio Mané", "Roberto Firmino", "Virgil van Dijk"],
            "correctOption": "Mohamed Salah"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which golfer was nicknamed the 'Golden Bear' and holds the record for the most major championship wins?",
            "options": ["Arnold Palmer", "Gary Player", "Jack Nicklaus", "Tom Watson"],
            "correctOption": "Jack Nicklaus"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which bowler holds the record for the most wickets taken in Test cricket as of 2023?",
            "options": ["Muttiah Muralitharan", "Shane Warne", "James Anderson", "Anil Kumble"],
            "correctOption": "James Anderson"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who won the 2023 Masters Tournament?",
            "options": ["Tiger Woods", "Jordan Spieth", "Rory McIlroy", "Justin Thomas"],
            "correctOption": "Jordan Spieth"
        }
    ],
    
    "hard": [
        {
            "question": "In the history of the UEFA Champions League, which club has the most titles?",
            "options": ["Manchester United", "FC Barcelona", "Real Madrid", "Bayern Munich"],
            "correctOption": "Real Madrid"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which golfer famously completed the 'Tiger Slam' by winning all four major championships consecutively in 2000-2001?",
            "options": ["Phil Mickelson", "Rory McIlroy", "Jordan Spieth", "Tiger Woods"],
            "correctOption": "Tiger Woods"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which team holds the longest winning streak in NBA history?",
            "options": ["Chicago Bulls", "Los Angeles Lakers", "Boston Celtics", "Golden State Warriors"],
            "correctOption": "Los Angeles Lakers"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is the only boxer to win world titles in eight different weight divisions?",
            "options": ["Muhammad Ali", "Mike Tyson", "Manny Pacquiao", "Floyd Mayweather Jr."],
            "correctOption": "Manny Pacquiao"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is the only boxer to win world titles in eight different weight divisions?",
            "options": ["Muhammad Ali", "Mike Tyson", "Manny Pacquiao", "Floyd Mayweather Jr."],
            "correctOption": "Manny Pacquiao"
        },
        {
            "question": "In which year did the first FIFA World Cup take place?",
            "options": ["1924", "1930", "1950", "1966"],
            "correctOption": "1930"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which athlete holds the record for the most Olympic gold medals in history?",
            "options": ["Usain Bolt", "Michael Phelps", "Serena Williams", "Simone Biles"],
            "correctOption": "Michael Phelps"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which team holds the longest winning streak in NBA history?",
            "options": ["Chicago Bulls", "Los Angeles Lakers", "Boston Celtics", "Golden State Warriors"],
            "correctOption": "Los Angeles Lakers"
        },
        {
            "question": "In which year did the Chicago Cubs win their most recent World Series before their 2016 championship?",
            "options": ["1924", "1945", "1984", "2008"],
            "correctOption": "1945"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which female tennis player was known as the 'Black Widow' for her dominance in the 1950s and 1960s?",
            "options": ["Maria Bueno", "Althea Gibson", "Martina Navratilova", "Billie Jean King"],
            "correctOption": "Althea Gibson"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which country hosted the 2019 Rugby World Cup?",
            "options": ["New Zealand", "South Africa", "England", "Japan"],
            "correctOption": "Japan"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is the only player to have won five Ballon d'Or awards as of 2023?",          
            "options": ["Cristiano Ronaldo", "Lionel Messi","Neymar", "Kaka"],
            "correctOption": "Lionel Messi"
        }
    ]
}